Guide to the David Richmond Gergen Papers, 1964-1999 (bulk 1971-1992) RL.00443
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession (2000-0356)
  - Gergen Subject Files S, 1975-1976 (Box 54)
    - Social Security (Box 54)
  - Gergen Subject Files S, continued (Box 55)
    - Secretary Simon, 4 folders (Box 55)
    - State and Local Governments, 3 folders (Box 55)
    - Statistics [Treasury Office-some admin. Confidentiality until released] (Box 55)
    - Steel Industry (Box 55)
    - Stein, Herbert (Box 55)
    - Stock Market/Stock Ownership/Stocks (Box 55)
  - Subject Files T-W, 1975-1976 (Box 55)
    - News Summary Project (Box 55)
    - Dave Gergen's Chron1972 April (Box 55)
      [includes job and staff memos; administratively confidential mats in 3rd folder]
    - TV Station Texts (Box 55)
    - TV Station Texts (Box 55)
    - $2 Bill (Box 55)
    - Unemployment (Box 55)
    - Utilities (Box 55)
    - Vital Speeches of the Day, 2 folders (Box 55)
  - Subject Files T-W, continued (Box 56)
    - Thomas, Jerry (Undersecretary-Treasury) (Box 56)
    - Trip with Simon [around the world] (Box 56)
    - Tax Proposal Response, 2 folders (Box 56)
    - Texas (Box 56)
    - Trade (Box 56)
    - Treasury Papers (Box 56)
    - Wage and Price Controls (Box 56)
    - Economic Reports-Charles Walker (Box 56)
    - Walker, Charles M. (Box 56)
    - Welfare (Box 56)
    - What Is Right in America? (Box 56)
    - Working People (Box 56)
  - Notebooks (Box 56)
    - Nine O'clock Meetings (Box 56)
    - News Summaries-1974 June -1974 July, 3 folders (Box 56)
    - Cabinet Meetings,1973-1974, 3 folders (Box 56)
    - [Memos by Gergen],1974, 2 folders (Box 56)
  - George Van Cleve (Box 57)
  - New York City Letters, Etc. (Box 57)
  - SOTU [State of the Union Address] drafts (Gergen et al.),1976 (Box 57)
  - DG Chron files1972 May-1972 August, 17 folders (Box 58)
  - Alphabetical Subject Files,1975-1980 (Box 59)
    - Abortion (Box 59)
    - Advocates, 2 folders (Box 59)
    - Busing, 2 folders (Box 59)
    - Congress (Box 59)
    - Corporations (Box 59)
    - CIA (Box 59)
    - Debates (Box 59)
    - Defense (Box 59)
    - Democratic Convention (Box 59)
    - Democratic Convention - TV Monitor (Box 59)
    - Democratic Platform (Box 59)
    - Drug Abuse (Box 59)
    - Energy Bill Signing Statement (Box 59)
    - Energy Policy (Box 59)
    - Energy Proposal- slides, 3 folders (Box 59)
    - Ethnic Groups (Box 59)
    - Ford (Box 59)
    - Foreign Policy, 2 folders (Box 59)
    - Freedom, Medal of (Box 59)
    - Future File (Box 59)
    - Ideas (Box 59)
    - Jobs (Box 59)
    - Multi-National Corporation (Box 59)
    - News Calendar (Box 59)
    - Olympics (Box 59)
    - Panama (Box 59)
    - Presidential Messages (Box 59)
    - Presidential Speeches (1974-1975) (Box 59)
    - Texas Briefing Book (Box 59)
  - [In the back of the Alphabetical Subject Files Box, BUT not in alphabetical order] (Box 60)
    - New England (Box 60)
    - New England Editors Speech (Box 60)
    - 60 Minutes, Maritime Report (Box 60)
    - Newspaper Clippings (copies of) - Monday,1976 November 1 (Box 60)
    - Attorney General Summary (Box 60)
    - Bicentennial Speeches, 2 folders (Box 60)
    - Material Prepared for the **[a symbol - looks like mathematical pi] (Box 60)
    - Debate (Box 60)
    - Second Debate File,1976 Debate (Box 60)
    - Bicentennial - 1976 July 4 (Box 60)
    - Bicentennial Task Force (Box 60)
    - Bicentennial Speeches of Ford -1976 July 1-1976 July 5, 3 folders; one in oversize box 4 (Box 60)
    - Bicentennial TV Clip, 2 folders (Box 60)
  - [Unordered material from another box] (Box 60)
    - Broadcasting -Equal Time, 2 folders (Box 60)
    - Book Notes,1977, 2 folders (Box 60)
    - Simon-Old Speeches,1974-1975 (Box 60)
  - #11 Personal Letter; Telephone Logs; Mid-East Mementos; RN Photos; Schedule for USSR Trip; Personal Notes (Box 61)
    - Letters: To Dave Gergen, 1973-1974, 2 folders (Box 61)
    - Telephone Memorandum (DG),1974, 5 folders (Box 61)
    - Dial Directory for White House Use Only (Box 61)
    - The Clearest Choice,1972 (Box 61)
      [published transcripts of PresidentNixon's radio addresses]
    - [Loose notes],1973, 2 folders (Box 61)
    - [Unlabeled notes], 1972, 5 folders (Box 61)
    - Dave Gergen-Writing File (Box 61)
    - Congratulatory Notes (DG),1973 (Box 61)
    - Dave Gergen-Purchase of Home,1973 (Box 61)
    - Visit of PresidentNixon to the Middle East,1974 June 10-1974 June 19: Fact Sheets and Speech Material (Box 61)
    - [Transcripts of exchange of remarks between PresidentNixon and various heads of state,1974] (Box 61)
    - Visit by RichardNixon to Syrian Arab Republic,1974 June 15-1974 June 16, 2 folders (Box 61)
    - [Israel material] (Box 61)
    - [Color photos-Nixon's visit to Middle East] (Box 61)
    - [Black and white photos of PresidentNixon] (Box 61)
    - [Color photos of PresidentNixon] (Box 61)
    - [Black and white photos of military man receiving The Meritorious Service Medal] (Box 61)
    - Visit of PresidentNixon to the Middle East,1974 June 10-1974 June 19: Fact Sheets and Speech Material (Box 61)
  - Govt. Regulation (Box 62)
  - Energy articles in Fortune from1978 June 5 to present (Box 62)
  - Eli Lilly (Box 62)
  - Antidumping case, legal memorandum,1978 (Box 62)
  - Political clippings,1979 January 2-1979 January 4, 3 folders (Box 62)
  - Political clippings,1979 January 2-1979 January 4, 3 folders (Box 62)
  - News Digest Issues1977, 4 folders (Box 62)
  - Correspondence for Public Opinion (Box 62)
  - Reports and Papers, 2 folders (Box 62)
    - Written statement by Michael Samuels, Senate Hearing on Rhodesia (Box 62)
    - The Hickman Novastill (Box 62)
    - Regulation - Some Private Costs and Strategies for Change (Box 62)
    - Is There a Concurring Majority about Northern Ireland? (Box 62)
    - Initial working paper on political strategy (Box 62)
    - The Playboy Report on American Men, 1977 (Box 62)
    - Audience Measurement Procedures, SMRB Report (Box 62)
  - Articles, 2 folders (Box 62)
  - Drafts of Gergen's articles and speeches, 2 folders (Box 62)
  - Miscellaneous papers (Box 62)
  - Issue Coordinators for GeorgeBush (Box 62)
  - Book Notes,1977, 2 folders (Box 62)
  - [News Conference Transcripts],1975, 2 folders (Box 62)
  - Press Statement for WES,1975 April (Box 62)
  - Miscellaneous Speech and Remarks for RN,1973-1974 (Box 63)
    - Dave Gergen Reading File:1972 January-1972 March, 2 folders (Box 63)
    - Writers Schedules (Box 63)
    - DG Taxes File (Box 63)
    - Miscellaneous Speeches and Remarks for RN,1973-1974, 3 folders (Box 63)
    - Gergen Selective Service, 2 folders (Box 63)
    - Gergen Selective Service, 2 folders (Box 63)
    - Herbert Humphrey (Box 63)
    - Humphrey-Hawkins Bill (Box 63)
    - ICC [Interstate Commerce Commission](Mike's Study), 2 folders (Box 63)
    - ICC [Interstate Commerce Commission] (Box 63)
    - Barry Goldwater (Box 63)
    - Goldwin, Bob (Box 63)
    - Government Regulations (Box 63)
    - Governors (Box 63)
    - Gov't. Debt and GNP (Box 63)
    - California Trip (Box 63)
    - [Churchill Lecture] (Box 63)
    - Britain (Box 63)
    - Budgets (Box 63)
    - Governor Ed [Jerry] Brown, 2 folders (Box 63)
  - Personnel Resumes [not including materials with SS#s], 2 folders (Box 64)
  - Writing Candidates [not including materials with SS#s], 3 folders (Box 64)
  - Speeches-NonTreasury,1974-1975, 3 folders (Box 64)
  - [WES-Speeches and background],1974, 4 folders (Box 64)
    Including Energy and Cargo Preference
  - [Reagan Speeches],1977 (Box 64)
    Including CAL GOP and National Press Club
  - [Subject Files],1977, 2 folders (Box 64)
    Including Desertification, CIA, AEI Regulatory Article, and Unlabeled
  - [Other Speeches] (Box 64)
    Including President Carter's State of the Union1978, and Roy Ash at the Swiss Chamber of Commerce,1977
  - Ford Dinner (Box 64)
  - Campaign; DG Handwritten Notes, 1976 (Box 64)
    [continued in boxes 69 and 70]
    - Eucharistic Congress (1976 October 8) (Box 64)
    - 1976 Elections (Box 64)
    - Delegates (Box 64)
    - Southern Trip (Box 64)
    - Ford-Two Year Report (Box 64)
    - Ford (Interviews) (Box 64)
    - DG Handwritten Notes (Box 64)
    - Dole, Robert (Box 64)
  - WES Speech and Testimony,1975 February-1975 April (Box 65)
    - Background--Knox County Rep. 1975 April 3 (Box 65)
    - Cattle Raisers Association 1975 March 15, 2 folders (Box 65)
    - Gardner--Kansas City (Jr. Achiev)1975 March 25 (Box 65)
    - Subcom on Intl Economics, JEC, 1975 March 24 (Box 65)
    - Talking Points, Conser Union, 1975 March 22 (Box 65)
    - Background, Tlkg Pts, Cons Un., 1975 March 22 (Box 65)
    - Cleveland World Affairs Conference, 1975 March 21 (Box 65)
    - Background, Clev. Wld. Aff. Conf. 1975 March 31 (Box 65)
    - WES--Alf London Lecture, Kansas, 1975 March 18 (Box 65)
    - Background--Alf Lecture, 1975 March 18 (Box 65)
    - National Newspaper Assoc (DC), 1975 March 14 (Box 65)
    - Background, Natl News Assoc (DC), 1975 March 14 (Box 65)
    - Testimony--House SubCommittee on Appropriations, 1975 March 13 (Box 65)
    - Talking Points for RAMS, 1975 March 13 (Box 65)
    - Talking Points--Y--Group, 1975 March 10 (Box 65)
    - Girard Nat'l Bank, Phila, 1975 March 10 (Box 65)
    - Testimony--Senate Finance Com, 1975 March 5 (Box 65)
    - Background, Senate Finance Comm, 1975 March 5 (Box 65)
    - DeMolay, Henry Dormann Tribute, 1975 March 5 (Empty folder) (Box 65)
    - WES--Before House Ways and Means, 1975 March 3 (Box 65)
    - Background, House Ways and Means, 1975 March 3 (Box 65)
    - Total Package--SF SPCH, LIEB: PITTS.TP, 1975 March 3 (Box 65)
    - WES--Commonwealth Speech, 1975 February 28 (Box 65)
    - Background--Commonwealth Speech, 1975 February 28 (Box 65)
    - WES--Nat'l Assoc. of Counties, 1975 February 26 (Box 65)
    - WES-BKGD INFO. Nat'l Assoc. Cnts., 1975 February 26 (Box 65)
    - Testimony--House Budget Comm., 1975 February 25 (Box 65)
    - Background, House Budget Comm Test, 1975 February 25 (Box 65)
    - WES--Inst. Of Foreign Affrs. 1975 February 25, Empty folder (Box 65)
    - unspecified (Box 65)
  - WES1975 November 12-1975 December 17 (Box 66)
    - Background Material-State of the Union, 1975, 4 folders (Box 66)
    - Background-Detroit Speech (Box 66)
    - American Farm Bureau Federation, 1975 January 6 (Box 66)
    - Senate Budget Committee, 1974 December 17 (Box 66)
    - Remarks-Deputy Secretary Gardner, 1974 December 17 (Box 66)
    - Myths of Our Economy-by Sidney Jones, 2 folders (Box 66)
    - WES-Background-Talking Points-Business Council, 1974 December 12, 2 folders (Box 66)
    - Background-Hoover Institution Luncheon, 1974 December 6 (Box 66)
    - SSG-American Banking Institute, 1974 December 5 (Box 66)
    - WES-Before the Saints and Sinners, 1974 December 5 (Box 66)
    - WES-Talking Points: Economic Briefing, 1974 December 4 (Box 66)
    - WES-Talking Points: New GOP Congressmen, 1974 December 4 (Box 66)
    - WES-Q&A material, 1974 December 4 (Box 66)
    - WES-Statement Supporting Frank Zarb, 1974 December 4 (Box 66)
    - WES-Before the International Finance House Committee on Banking and Currency, 1974 December 3 (Box 66)
    - Talking Points, Pittsburgh Businessmen, 1974 December 2 (Box 66)
    - WES-Background Material-Talking Points for Bull Elephants-1974 November 26 (Box 66)
    - WES-Joint Economic Committee, 1974 November 25 (Box 66)
    - WES-Background Material-Statement for Sugar Hearings, 1974 November 25 (Box 66)
    - WES-Background Material-Rubber Manufacturer's Association, 1974 November 21 (Box 66)
    - WES-Background Material-Council on Foreign Affairs-1974 November 20 (Box 66)
    - WES-Background Material-Talking Points to Representatives of Women's Organizations, 1974 November 20 (Box 66)
    - Council on Foreign Affairs, 1974 November 19 (Box 66)
    - WES-Talking Points on the Economy, 1974 November 18 (Box 66)
    - WES-Background Material-Foreign Trade Council-NYC-1974 November 18, 2 folders (Box 66)
    - WJ Conference of Mayors-1974 November 14 (Box 66)
    - WES-Background Material for the American Petroleum Institute, 1974 November 12 (Box 66)
    - WES-Background Material for Housing Speech at Time Conference, 1974 November 8 (Box 66)
  - Supplies (Box 67)
    - Department of Treasury News and Press Briefing (Box 67)
    - Playboy Interview (Box 67)
    - Readers Digest Article (Box 67)
    - Readers Digest Article Background, 4 folders (Box 67)
    - Ripon Society (Box 67)
    - Foreign Investment Article, 3 folders (Box 67)
    - Fortune Article (Box 67)
    - Atlantic Magazine (Box 67)
    - Untitled, 2 folders (Box 67)
    - Florida Trip (Box 67)
    - San Francisco Trip (Box 67)
    - Magazine Articles (Box 67)
    - American Airways (Box 67)
    - Foreign Investment in the U.S. (Box 67)
    - Speeches--Treasury Personnel (Box 67)
    - Simon Interviews (Box 67)
    - Treasury Information (Box 67)
    - Vital Speeches of the Day,1974 December 1, Empty folder (Box 67)
    - Whalen, Dick (Box 67)
    - Wilson Visit (Box 67)
    - Reading (Box 67)
  - Personal (Box 67)
    - News Summaries (Box 67)
    - Personnel Resumes (Box 67)
    - Gergen Personal (Personnel Stuff) (contain Gergen's personal financial records), 1-2 of 4 folders (Box 67)
  - Personal (cont.) (Box 68)
    - Gergen Personal (Personnel Stuff), 3-4 of 4 folders (Box 68)
    - Dave Gergen Personal, 2 folders (Box 68)
    - President's Press Conf.1976 October 20 (Box 68)
    - State of the Union (Box 68)
    - Travel Junk (Box 68)
    - National Conference of Catholic Bishops (Box 68)
    - TV Guide Interview (Box 68)
    - TV Guide Briefing Copies (Box 68)
    - Time Interview (Box 68)
    - Interview: Washington Post (Box 68)
    - Public Relations World Congress (Box 68)
    - American G.I. Forum (Box 68)
    - Congressional Candidates Platform Reception (Box 68)
    - Bicentennial Joint Boy/Girls Nation (Box 68)
    - Christian Broadcasting (Tape) (Box 68)
    - Political Questionnaire--Medical News (Box 68)
    - Harry Reasoner Briefing, 3 folders (Box 68)
    - Gergen Personal (Clips), 3 folders (Box 68)
    - Gergen Personal (Correspondence), 2 folders (Box 68)
    - Gergen Personal (Candidates), Empty folder (Box 68)
    - DRG--Life Insurance (Box 68)
    - [Article: The 1968 Presidential Election] (Box 68)
    - Copy of The Public Interest Number 42,1976 Winter (Box 68)
  - WES Speech File1975 September-1975 December (Box 69)
    - Delaware Bicentennial Speech, 1975 September 20, 2 folders (Box 69)
    - Upper Midwest Council, 1975 September 19, 2 folders (Box 69)
    - Associated Industries, NY-1975 September 18, 2 folders (Box 69)
    - Southern Governors-1975 September 15, 2 folders (Box 69)
    - Law Enforcement Center, Georgia, 1975 September 12, 2 folders (Box 69)
    - Friends of Buckley, NYC-1975 September 10, 2 folders (Box 69)
    - Talking Points-Freshmen Congressmen-1975 September 8 (Box 69)
    - Latin American Governors-1975 September 3, 2 folders (Box 69)
    - World Bank and IMF, 1975 September 2, 3 folders (Box 69)
    - WES-No. Carolina Speech-1975 January 20 (Box 69)
    - Associated Industries of Arizona, Phoenix, Arizona, 1975 December 15, 2 folders (Box 69)
    - US Citizens Congress Award, Washington, DC-1975 December 14, 2 folders (Box 69)
    - Houston Chamber of Commerce, Houston, TX, 1975 December 11, 2 folders (Box 69)
    - [Mutual Black Network Dinner, 1975 December 10] (Box 69)
    - Capital Formation Talking Points-1975 December 10 (Box 69)
    - Cong DuPont Dinner, Wilmington, Delaware-1975 December 8, 3 folders (Box 69)
  - Campaign 1976; DG Handwritten Notes (Box 69)
    [continued from box 64]
    - Campaign File #2, 2 folders (Box 69)
  - Campaign 1976; DG Handwritten Notes (continued) (Box 70)
    - Campaign Financing (Box 70)
    - Campaign, 13 folders (Box 70)
  - Mostly Personal Books and WG Hearing Books [actually contains WES Speeches,1975 June-1975 October] (Box 70)
    - Fund Bank Speech, 1975 October 8 (Box 70)
    - Gardner Remarks for Shultz, 1975 October 6 (Box 70)
    - CustomHouse Dedication, 1975 October 1 (Box 70)
    - Testimonial for Bob Steel-1975 July 31 (Box 70)
    - Talking Points-MD Republican Steering Committee-1975 July 28 (Box 70)
    - Ripon Society, Capitol Hill Club (Box 70)
    - Talking Points-Briefing for Sub-Cabinet, July 16 (Box 70)
    - Buffalo, NY-1975 July 14, 2 folders (Box 70)
    - Republican Women-1975 July 14 (Box 70)
    - Fiedler Luncheon-1975 July 11 (Box 70)
  - [WES Speeches,1975 June-1975 October], (continued) (Box 71)
    - Mayors-White House-1975 July 10 (Box 71)
    - Biloxi, Mississippi-1975 July 9, 2 folders (Box 71)
    - Radio Tape for 1975 July 4 (Box 71)
    - White House Session on Revenue Sharing-Background (Box 71)
    - NAACP Speech, Washington, DC-1975 July 2, 3 folders (Box 71)
    - Bennett Reception-1975 June 30 (Box 71)
    - Talking Points-Wharton-1975 June 26 (Box 71)
    - YAF Award (Box 71)
    - American Jewish Committee-1975 June 18 (Box 71)
    - Women's Day Speech-1975 June 18, 2 folders (Box 71)
    - Talking Points-TARS-1975, 1975 June 17, 2 folders (Box 71)
    - American Coal Association-1975 June 17, 2 folders (Box 71)
    - Amsterdam Speech-International Monetary Conference-1975 June 13, 3 folders (Box 71)
  - [Manuscript] (Box 71)
    - [To be picked up by Dave Gergen from Frederic V. Malek], 2 folders (Box 71)
    - [in Binder], 4 folders (Box 71)
  - Bill Simon-Radio, 2 folders (Box 72)
  - [Subject Files and speeches],1979, 3 folders (Box 72)
    Includes materials on energy and urban policy
  - Carter Campaign1976 (Box 72)
  - WES Speech File1975 November-1975 December (Box 72)
    - NBC Management Forum, New York (Box 72)
    - Calvin Bullock Forum, New York, 1975 November 26 (Box 72)
    - National Association of Counties Revenue Sharing Activities, 1975 November 18 (Box 72)
    - Hearst Articles, 5 folders (Box 72)
    - Jack Anderson Roast, Press Club, 1975 December 1, 2 folders (Box 72)
    - Background-Pacem in Terris IV, 1975 December 2 (Box 72)
    - Remarks on Receiving the Report of the Commission on Private Philanthropy and Public Needs, 1975 December 2 (Box 72)
  - WES Speech File,1975 November-1975 December, continued (Box 73)
    - Tax Foundation NY, 1975 December 3, 3 folders (Box 73)
    - Background-National Institute of Social Sciences' Awards Dinner, 1975 December 4 (Box 73)
  - HJC Hearings,1974 July 20, 1974 July 25-1974 July 26, 1974 July 30 (Box 73)
  - [Subject files] (Box 73)
    - Hudson Institute (Box 73)
    - Housing, 2 folders (Box 73)
    - Government Spending, 2 folders (Box 73)
    - Greenspan, Alan [speeches] (Box 73)
  - Subject Files I-M 1976 (Box 73)
    - Internal Revenue Service (Box 73)
    - International Economic Comparisons (Box 73)
    - International Monetary Fund (Box 73)
    - International Trade (Box 73)
    - Janeway, Eliot (Box 73)
    - Jefferson, Thomas (Box 73)
    - Jewish Banking (Box 73)
  - Subject Files I-M continued (Box 74)
    - Jones, Sid, 2 folders (Box 74)
    - Kahn, Herman (Hudson Institute) (Box 74)
    - Kissinger, [Henry], 6 folders (Box 74)
    - Koch, Noel (Box 74)
    - Labor (Box 74)
    - Law of the Sea (Box 74)
    - Massachusetts (Box 74)
  - Subject Files Q-S 1974-1975 (Box 74)
    - Quality of Life (Box 74)
    - Rationing File (Box 74)
    - Ravenel,Charles (Box 74)
    - Realism (Box 74)
    - Recovery (Box 74)
    - Religion (Box 74)
    - Reprints of Simon's Speeches (Box 74)
    - Revenue Sharing (Box 74)
    - Revitalization (Box 74)
    - Right Report, The (Box 74)
    - Rinfret, Pierre A. (Box 74)
    - Rockerfeller [Nelson] (Box 74)
    - Rumsfeld [Donald H.] (Box 74)
    - Sacred Cows (Box 74)
    - Securities Regulations (Box 74)
    - Shultz, George P. (Box 74)
  - Subject Files Q-S, continued (Box 75)
    - Sindlinger, Albert, 5 folders (Box 75)
    - Material Recommended by Secretary Simon, 5 folders (Box 75)
  - Photos of Gerald Ford (Box 75)
  - Gergen's resumes (Box 75)
  - Jimmy Carter Quote Book Update (Box 75)
  - [Subject Files],1975-1977 (Box 75)
    - Cattle Raising (Box 75)
    - Television-Fairness Doctrine (Box 75)
    - Sindlinger (Box 75)
    - Simon Reading Materials [includes copies of WES speeches] (Box 75)
    - Republican Papers (Box 75)
    - Regulation by Government (Box 75)
    - Free Enterprise (Box 75)
    - Burns, Arthur (Box 75)
    - Bureaucracy-Growth in Government (Box 75)
    - Budgeting-Zero Based (Box 75)
    - Political Clippings, 1978 December 5, 2 folders (Box 75)
    - Polls and Studies from Newspapers, 1978 December 5 (Box 75)
  - WES1975 January-1975 February (Box 76)
    - WES--Hse. Approp. Cmte. 1975 February 18 (Box 76)
    - WES--Bkgd Hse. Appropriations Test 1975 February 18 (Box 76)
    - WES--Background Material for Bond Club (1975 February 18 ), 2 folders (Box 76)
    - WES--Hse. Interstate and Foreign Commerce Subcmte Energy and Power 1975 February 18, 2 folders (Box 76)
    - WES--Talking Points: Boca Raton (1975 February 12) (Box 76)
    - WES--Paterson Speech, NYC, 1975 February 11 (Box 76)
    - Background--Payroll Savings Speech (Box 76)
    - ES--Petroleum Import Fees Senate Finance Comm. 1975 February 10, 2 folders (Box 76)
    - WES--(Debt Ceiling) Sen Fin Cmte 1975 February 10, 2 folders (Box 76)
    - WES--Material for the Farleigh Dickinson Speech 5 February 1975, 2 folders (Box 76)
    - WES--Joint Econ. Cmte. 1975 February 5 (Box 76)
    - WES--Background Material--House Banking Committee, 1975 February 4 (Box 76)
    - WES--Background Material on Testimony on Reuss Bill, 1975 February 4 (Box 76)
    - WES--Before the Subcommittee on Financial Markets 1975 January 30 (Box 76)
    - Background, Senate Finance Comm. 1975 January 30 (Box 76)
    - Background, Quadrangular Conf 27 1975 January (Box 76)
    - Foreign Editors Briefing 1975 January 27 (Box 76)
    - WES--Testimony for Ways and Means 1975 January 23--(Final Draft), 3 folders (Box 76)
    - Gardner--Homebuilders in Dallas, 1975 January 19 (Box 76)
    - WES--Payroll Savings Luncheon, 1975 January 19 (Box 76)
    - Briefing for Presidential Spokesmen (Box 76)
    - State of the Union--Clippings, empty folder (Box 76)
    - WES--Speech Before Michigan Business Conference, U. of Mich.-1975 January 9 (Box 76)
  - Subject Files,1976-1977 (Box 77)
    - Yale University (Box 77)
    - EOB - Article (Box 77)
    - DRG - Personal papers (Box 77)
    - Sindlinger - January (Box 77)
    - Sindlinger (Box 77)
    - Simon - Coming Speeches (Box 77)
    - Bill Simon - Speeches (Box 77)
    - Polling Data (Box 77)
    - National Commission on Libraries (Box 77)
    - Malek Project, 2 folders (Box 77)
    - Bob Kasten (Box 77)
    - February Group (Box 77)
    - Elizabeth Dole (Box 77)
    - Deaver and Hannaford, Inc. (Box 77)
    - Brook/RNC (Box 77)
  - The Daily Newssummary, Prospectus (Box 77)
  - Regulation, 1977 September-1997 October (Box 77)
  - Organizational meeting: executive news summary (Box 77)
  - Photos of Gerald Ford (Box 77)
  - unspecified (Box 77)
  - Subject Files,1974-1976 (Box 78)
    - Chron File (N.L.S.) (Box 78)
    - Gaynor, Janie (BYU Speech) (Box 78)
    - Bryan Devereux Hickman (Box 78)
    - Memos from Gergen, 1976 (Box 78)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 78)
    - Maps (Box 78)
    - Memos Received (Box 78)
    - Memos to Simon (Box 78)
    - Letter to President, Re: Trip (Box 78)
    - Economic Comments (Box 78)
    - Future Speeches (Box 78)
    - Interns (Box 78)
    - 3 Week trip with Simon (Box 78)
    - Biographical Sketch of Stephen S. Gardner (Box 78)
    - Biographical Sketch of William E. Simon (Box 78)
    - Memos, 1975 (Box 78)
    - Notes from WES, 1974 October 9 (Box 78)
    - Small Business (Box 78)
    - Capacity Utilization (Box 78)
    - Health (Box 78)
    - Airline Regulations (Box 78)
    - Anti-trust (Box 78)